[Music]
Today our first company is Cama Holdings
Limited Chaha
2641 company is going to announce
dividend of 1775 fils its ex date
is 28th March recorded on 28th March
[Music]
and our next company is TVS Holding
Limited Company Bach Raha Hai
8949 company is going to announce
dividend of 93 fils its ex date is 28th March
recorded on 28th March
and our next company is Nepal Investment
Limited Company Katchar
11133 company is going to announce dividend of
₹ whose ex date is 27th March recorded on 27th
March
[Music]
and our next company is Capital Trade
Links Limited Kani Katchar ₹ 2 company is going to
announce stock bonus 1:1
ratio whose ex date is 2nd April
recorded on 2nd April
[Music]
and our next company is Dot Ready Laboratories
Limited Kachar
1177 company is going to announce board meeting on 9th May which purpose will be
dividend plus
[Music]
result and our next company  Kansai Rolak
Paints Ltd. Kutch 2237 company is going to announce
board meeting on 6th May and purpose is going to be
dividend plus
result and our agri company SCL
Technology Ltd.
K4 company is going to announce board
meeting on 2nd April and purpose is going to be
dividend plus
result [music] and our agri ICICI Lombard
General Insurance Co. Ltd. Kutch
1779 company is going to announce board meeting on
15th April and purpose is going to be dividend
plus
result and our next company Aan Housing
Ltd. K00 company is going to announce
board meeting on 28th March and purpose is going to be
dividend and our next company Hindustan
Uni Labour Ltd. Kutch 2271
company is going to announce board meeting on
24th April and purpose is going to be dividend
plus result
[music]